(Amy:)You know what? Good.
(Amy:)I tried to get back together
with Sheldon; he shot me down;
(Amy:)Dave likes me.
(Amy:)Maybe intimate
is what I need.
(Sheldon:)You sure?
(Bernadette:)You've never really been
with a man.
(Bernadette:)Do you really want to start
with one that's six-foot-seven?
(Amy:)Why not?
'Cause it's like taking
your driver's test in a bus.
(Raj:)Maybe we should post a comment
back to our fan and thank him.
(Howard:)What should we write?
How 'bout, uh...
Oh, how 'bout,
"We might be
Footprints on the Moon,
(Raj:)but your kind words sent
us over the moon."
(Howard:)Someday you're gonna make
an amazing grandma.
(Raj:)What do you
want to write?
(Howard:)Something bad-ass,
you know, like...
"Thanks for diggin' our vibe.
"We'll keep rockin'
if you keep rollin'."
(Raj:)Dude, if I was wearing a bra,